Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.twelve Mss.B.B61.inventory12
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents S
  - Steiney, Lore v. d. (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 5; 4p
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 24; 3p
    - To Boas, 1935 July 5; 4p
    - To Boas, 1935 Sep. 8; 4p
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 20; 2p
    - To Lehmann, Mrs., 1931 Dec. 21; 6p
    - To Lehmann, Mrs., 1932 Mar. 28; 4p
  - Steinhagen, Gustav (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 26; 2p
  - Steinitz, Ernest (Box 85)
    - see Steinitz, Kate, 1936 Sep. 5
  - Steinitz, Mrs. Kate (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1936 Sep. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Jan. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Sep. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 20; 1p
  - Steinmann, Gustav (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 29; 1p
  - Steinthal, H. (Box 85)
    - To Boas, 1888 Nov. 15
  - Stejneger, Leonhard (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 8
    - To Boas, 1895 Nov. 26
    - To Boas, 1895 Dec. 11
    - To Boas, 1896 June 17
    - To Boas, 1897 Apr. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 9
  - Stella, Antonio (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1910 Sep. 30
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 14
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 27
  - Stelz, Ludwig (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 13; 3p
    - From Neisser, 1923 Jan. 29; 1p
    - To Reinhardt, Walter, 1922 Dec.; 2p
  - Stelzle, Charles (Box 85)
    - From Boas, 1938 May 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 June 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 May 5; 1p
      Enc: his Canadian and American "Good Neighbor" celebration
    - To Boas, 1938 May 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Nov. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 16; 1p
  - Stenlinger, P.
    - To Boas, 1923 July 11; 2p
  - Stenzel (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1931 May 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 July 2
    - From Boas, 1931 July 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 14; 1p
  - Stenzel, Berta (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 4; 2p
  - Stenzel, Julius (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1933 July 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 27; 1p
  - Stephenson, J. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1915 Dec. 11; 2p
  - Stern, Alfred K. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1934 Dec. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 July 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Aug. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Aug. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Mar. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Mar. 20; 1p
  - Stern, Bernhard, J. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, E. P., 1945 Oct. 24; 1p
  - Stern, Emil (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 20; 1p
  - Stern, Kurt G. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 25; 1p
  - Stern, Max (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 1; 1p
  - Stern, W. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 30; 2p
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 18; 2p
  - Sternberg, Leo (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1906 Aug. 9
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 1
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 15
    - From Boas, 1907 May 6
    - From Boas, 1907 May 7
    - From Boas, 1907 Sep. 27
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 12
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 12
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 5
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 2
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 6
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 11
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 15
    - From Boas, 1912 Aug. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 22
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 8
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 22
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 27
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 21
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 2
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 18
    - From Boas, 1914 Apr. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 May 6
    - From Boas, 1914 May 23
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 17; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 28
    - From Boas, 1924 May 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 29; 2p
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Aug. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 24
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 28
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 20
    - To Boas, 1908 May 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 July 17
    - To Boas, 1908 Sep. 29
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 7
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 21
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 28
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 28
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 18
    - To Boas, 1910 May 27
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 12
    - Found at end of Dec. 1911, 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 16
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 7
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1913 June 23
    - To Boas, 1914 May 26
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 28
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 21
    - To Boas, 1924 July 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Sep. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sep. 15; 2p
  - Sternberg, S. (Mrs. L.) (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Feb. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 May 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Sep. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Sep. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 June 10; 1p
  - Sternberger, E. M. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 20; 3p
    - To Boas, 1935 Sep. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 14; 1p
  - Sternburg (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 26; 1p
  - Sternburg (Box 86)
    - To Mr. Robert Thiem, 1904 Apr. 2; 1p
  - Sternburg, Speck v. baron (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1905 Feb. 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 29; 2p
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 18
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 28
  - Sternfeld, M.H. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 18; 1p
  - Stetson, John B. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 20
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 22
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 21
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 2
  - Stetz, Lud. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 13; 3p
  - Stevens (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 19
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 14
  - Stevens, David H. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1934 May 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 June 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1934 July 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 May 10; 2p
    - From Boas, 1935 May 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 May 2; 3p
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 June 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 May 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 May 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 14; 1p
  - Stevens, G. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1931 July 13; 1p
  - Stevens, E. W. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 28; 1p
  - Stevenson, B. L. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 15
  - Stevenson, Burton (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1927 July 30; 1p
  - Stevenson, P. H. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 16; 1p
  - Stevenson, S.Y. (Mrs. Cornelius) (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1893 Dec. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1894 Jan. 20
    - From Boas, 1895 Dec. 29
    - To Boas, 1893 Oct. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1893 Nov. 18
    - To Boas, 1893 Dec. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1893 Dec. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1903 May 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 May 12; 2p
  - Stewart, C. I. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1936 July 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 24; 1p
    - see Boas, F. (to Kane, F.F.), 1940 Dec. 26
    - To Boas, 1936 July 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 June 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 23; 2p
  - Stewart, Donald O. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 12; 1p
    - To Boas
    - see Brooks, V.W., 1938 Nov. 22
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 7
    - see Brewster, Dorothy, 1939 July 18
    - To Boas
      see Boas, F. (open Letter)
    - Found at end of Dec. 1939, 1940 Apr. 9; 1p
  - Stewart, E. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 26
  - Stewart, F. M. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 17; 2p
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 14; 1p
  - Stewart, Florence (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 1; 1p
  - Stewart, Maxwell S. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 16; 1p
    - To Boas
    - see Brewster, Dorothy, 1939 July 18
    - To Finkelstein, M. I., 1940 Dec. 4; 1p
  - Stewart, T. B. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1939 May 3; 1p
  - Stewart, T. D. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1938 June 17; 1p
  - Steye, G. E. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 3
  - Stieglitz, Julius (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 18
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 22
  - Stieglitz, Leo (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1936 May 4; 2p
    - To Boas
    - Found at end of Dec. 1936, 1p
      Re lips, J. E.
  - Stintze, von (Box 86)
    - To Boas
    - Found at end of Dec. 1911, 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 May 14; 1p
  - Stirling, Matthew W. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 5; 2p
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 May 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1930 May 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 May 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 June 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 June 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 June 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 June 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 July 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 May 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 May 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 May 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 May 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 June 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Aug. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 10; 2p
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 June 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 July 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 July 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Oct. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 July 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Apr. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Aug. 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 May 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 June 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Jan. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Oct. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 May 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 12; 2p
    - Enc. Abbot, C., 1930 May 19; 1p
    - (to Sec'y of State), 1930 May 16
    - Enc. White, F., 1930 June 9; 1p
    - (to Abbot, C.G.), 1930 June 5
    - To Boas, 1930 June 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 May 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 May 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 May 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 June 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 July 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Sep. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 July 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Aug. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 June 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Feb. 24; 1p
    - From Hertz, R., 1936 June 13
    - From Parsons, E. C., 1932 Sep. 13
    - From Unwin, J.D., 1929 June 21
    - Enc with Unwin, J.D., 1929 Oct. 12
    - To Unwin, J.D., 1929 July 2; 1p
    - Enc. with Unwin, J.D., 1929 Oct. 12
  - Stix, A. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1934 Sep. 21; 2p
      (open letter)
  - Stock, C. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 21; 1p
  - Stockton Profile Gauge Corporation (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 28; 1p
    - see Whitney, E., 1935 Apr. 4; 1p
  - Stoddard, G. D. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 13; 1p
  - Stoecker, H. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 12; 1p
  - Stofflet, Elliott H. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Mar. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 135 Dec. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 July 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 31; 1p
  - Stoffmann, G. K. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 15; 7p
  - Stoiber, L. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1930 June 12; 2p
    - Enc: Boys and girls of the world. Huss, B. (Open letter), 1929 Dec. 12
  - Stokes (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 14
    - From Gregg, Richard B., 1926 June 18
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1906 Sep. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Feb. 8; 1p
  - Stokes, Anson P. Jr. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1905 May 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Sep. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Feb. 9; 1p
  - Stokes, Brett (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 24; 1p
  - Stokes, F. W. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1902 Dec. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 June 22
  - Stokes, S. E. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 13; 3p
  - Stokowski, Leopold (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 11; 1p
  - Stolbreither (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1928 May 8; 1p
  - Stolley, Herman (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1938 May 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 May 10; 1p
      Enc: Organizations comprising United Anti-Nazi Council
  - Stolpe, H. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1903 July 24
    - From Boas, 1903 July 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 July 1; 4p
  - Stolz, B. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 18; 2p
  - Stone, F. W. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1910 June 8
  - Stone, Harlan F. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Oct. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 8; 2p
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 June 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 16; 1p
  - Stone, Lauson H. (Box 86)
    - From Boas
    - see Boas, F. (to Lombardo, Carmyn J.), 1940 Oct. 14
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 6; 1p
  - Stone, May (Box 86)
    - see Pettit, K. E., 1908 Jan.
  - Stone, Paul (Box 86)
    - see Willner, Alan, 1940 Nov. 4
    - See Boas, F. (to Willner, Alan) and Stone, Paul, 1940 Nov. 7
  - Stone, T. A. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1931 May 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 15; 1p
  - Stone, Thomas E. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 22; 1p
  - Stonebridge, J. H. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1939 July 3; 1p
  - Stoppelaer, F. de (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1905 Feb. 4
    - From Boas, 1905 June 1
    - From Boas, 1906 May 24
  - Storey, T.A. (Thomas) (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 Sep. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 1; 1p
  - Storm, D. Ernest (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 23; 2p
  - Storm, E. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 May 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 18; 4p
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 20; 1p
  - Storm, Harry (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Apr. 15; 1p
  - Storm, P. J. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1931 May 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 21; 1p
  - Storsberg, F. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 4
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 1
  - Story, D. M. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 2
  - Stott, L. H. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 30; 1p
  - Stout, A. B. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1926 Aug. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 6; 1p
  - Stout, Guy A. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1940 Oct. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Jan. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Oct. 19; 1p
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 15
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 14
  - Stowell, E. C. (Box 86)
    - From Levy, M. P., 1932 Apr. 7
    - Enc. with Levy, M. P., 1932 Apr. 7
  - Stoyle, R. S. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 11; 1p
  - Strang, Gerald (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1931 Sep. 21; 1p
  - Stratton, G. M. Dr. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 22; 2p
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 11; 1p
    - Enc. Report of the Amer. Anthrop. Ass. committee appoin for a closer cooperation with the National Research Council, 1926 Feb. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 24
    - From Boas, 1926 Apr. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Apr. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 May 10; 1p
    - Enc. Boas, F. (to Wissler, C.), 1926 June 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 June 7
    - From Boas, 1926 June 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 10; 1p
    - Enc.: Report of A.A.A. WN.R.C., 1926 Mar. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 June 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 June 15; 1p
    - From Hedlicka, A., 1926 Apr. 15
    - see Boas, F. (to Woodworth, R.S.), 1931 Sep. 2
  - Straus, Mrs. Nathan D. (Box 86)
    - see Boas, F. (to Lombardo, C.J.), 1940 Oct. 14
  - Straus, Nellie (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1918 Oct. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 30; 1p
  - Straus, O. S. (Box 86)
    - see Schwab, G.H., 1906 May 26
  - Straus, William L., Jr. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1919 July 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 June 22; 1p
  - Strayer, George D. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1910 June 7
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 25
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1910 June 11
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 12; 1p
  - Strecker und Schroder (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Aug. 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 June 8; 6p
    - To Boas, 1924 Sep. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Sep. 9; 3p
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 29; 4p
    - To Lehmann, W., 1921 Nov. 16; 2p
    - To Seler-Sachs, C., 1924 July 11; 2p
    - Enc. with Strecker und Schroder (to Seler-Sachs, C.), 1924 Aug. 6
    - To Seler-Sachs, C., 1924 Aug. 6; 1p
      Enc. Strecker und Schroder
    - To (Seler-Sachsc C., 1924 July 11
  - Street, Arthur I. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1892 Dec. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1893 Dec. 27; 2p
  - Streitberg, Wilhelm (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1922 Dec. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 24; 2p
  - Strelnikov (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1936 May 12
  - Strong, Benjamin (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 16
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 6
    - To Boas, 1908 Sep. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 2
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 7
  - Strong, Duncan (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1934 Aug. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 May 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 Sep. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 May 26; 2p
  - Strong, W. D. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1927 May 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 May 3; 1p
  - Stroock, Sol M. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Aug. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Aug. 24; 1p
  - Strother, Elizabeth (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1939 Sep. 20; 1p
  - Strube, L. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1915 Oct. 4
  - Strunsky, Shaba (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1940 Nov. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Sep. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Nov. 15; 1p
  - Strzygowski, J. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar.
  - Stuart, Harold G. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 June 23; 1p
  - Stucklen, Richard H. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1937 May 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 May 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 May 26; 1p
  - Stude, C. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1923 May 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 24; 1p
  - Student Council Peace Comm. to President (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 6; 1p
  - Student Review (Box 86)
    see Peters, Harold N.
  - Students and Teachers of New York (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1932; 2p
  - Stuhlmann, Franz (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1920 June 18; 1p
  - Stülpnagel, C. (Doris) (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 25; 4p
  - Stulpnagel, F. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 21
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 30; 2p
  - Stülpner, K. (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1932 Mar. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 July 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 4; 2p
  - Stülpner, W. (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 8
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 12; 2p
  - Stumpf, Carl (Box 86)
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 12
    - From Boas, 1924 Apr. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1886 Jan. 21
    - To Boas, 1886 Jan. 25
    - To Boas, 1886 Feb. 21
    - To Boas, 1886 Mar. 8
    - To Boas, 1886 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1886 Apr. 1
    - To Boas, 1895 May 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1895 July 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1895 July 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 July 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1912 May 10; 2p
    - to Boas, 1924 Mar. 12; 3p
    - to Boas, 1927 July 5; 2p
    - to Boas, 1928 Feb. 18; 2p
  - Sturgis, Appleton (Box 86)
    - To Boas, 1887 Dec. 19
    - Deutsch Ausland Institut
      See Wanner, Theodore H.
  - Sturtevant, E. H. (Box 86)
    - see Edgerton, F. Enc., 1938 Jan. 31
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 July 8; 1p
    - Attached outline of answers, 1919 May 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Sep. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 May 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Ja. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 July 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 4; 1p
    - see Bloomfield, L, Bolling, G. and Sturtevant, E.H., 1924 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 15; 1p
    - Enc. notice of the Linguistic Institute, 1927 Sep. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Sep. 30; 1p